Reference architecture that is just micro service based.
This means we have a container platform,
Thus, a Kubernetes platform that we operate inside our walls.
Since we work with the safety that we still do, we have, among other things, Air-Gapped environments
Thus, air -grated environments.
After all, we look at brand new frameworks both in backend and in Frontend.
In addition to Frontend developers, we have also started using UX designers,
To find both new work methods and new ways of presenting information
To meet the needs of our young people.
So it will be a lot more
modern interface from the Java Swing components that look like they come from